MIA CONTRERAS

STUDENT



Mia718a@gmail.com

221 Far Hills Dr, Bolingbrook IL,

https://linktr.ee/xxpineapplesxx7

ABOUT MF

A full-time student majoring in computer science. Highly driven and love to meet others. Efficient and hardworking when needed to meet the priorities of others. Experienced with organizing and leading educational activities. Devoted to promoting a positive experience!

SKILLS

- Strong Communication
- Staff Training
- Dish Preparation
- Behavior Management
- Problem-Solving
- Time Management
- Creative
- Leadership

EDUCATION

HIGH SCHOOL

Bolingbrook Highschool 2018-2021

3 year graduate

NEHS

COLLEGE

Lewis University

2021- Present

Computer Science Major

Give Something Back Recipient

ACM member

EXPERIENCE

CONTENT CREATOR

20+ Brands/Companies

2020 - Present

- Knowledgeable and up-to-date in different social media guidelines
- Track data and insights and adjust strategy and content regularly based on metrics
- Develop creative and engaging on-trend content to grow presence across a range of social platforms

CASHIER

Scene75 Entertainment Center

2021-Present

- Knowledgeable on menu and food preparation
- Operated cash register, took orders and served food
- Energizes people and is passionate about guest service.

CASHIER/CARVER/SERVER

Boston Market

2021 - 2022

- Trained new team members in cash, stock and customer service
- · Operated cash register, took orders and served food
- · Prepare and cut food needed in a timely manner